# Piotr Karszny

#### Contact

Email: piotr.karszny@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/piotrkarszny

#### **Profile**

An experienced PHP developer, and currently a Go enthusiast. Immense Linux fan.

Embraces transparency, and communication as a significant aspect of the teamwork. Always wiling to help, and leverages knowledge sharing as a driver for constant improvement of his abilities.

## **Employment**

Boxdrop / software engineer

07.2021 - NOW

Stack: PHP, GO, Docker, JS, MariaDB

STS Gaming Group / software engineer

01.2021 - 06.2021

Tech stack: PHP, JS, MySQL, Docker

Boldare / software engineer

04.2014 - 12.2020

Tech stack: PHP, JS, MySQL, Docker, Vagrant

**Studio-IT** — server infrastructure administrator

02.2011 - 03.2014

 $Maintained\ LINUX/WINDOWS\ infrastructure\ (web\ servers,\ e-mail,\ databases)$ 

Skills

Programming Languages PHP, GO, JavaScript, TypeScript

Database MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

 ${\bf Infrastructure}\quad {\bf Docker,\ Vagrant,\ Ansible}$ 

Cloud AWS, RDS, EC2, S3, DynamoDB

CI/CD Travis, GitLab-CI, GitHub Actions

Version Control Git, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket

Project/Team Management Agile, Scrum

### Education

University of Humanities and Economics in Łódź — engineer's degree 2003 – 2007 - computer science, computer networks